{
    "id": "a7f00ccca1a14b47b70a4e2196837b13",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I look forward to ……………………………….. from you.",
            "description": "When to is a preposition, it is followed by an ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "hear",
                "hearing",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It is Janet ……………………………… the phone. She wants to talk to you.",
            "description": "We say on the phone.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Is there anything interesting …………………………….. the radio tonight?",
            "description": "We say on the radio.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "over",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He met his future bride ……………………………. a party.",
            "description": "At is used in some common fixed expressions like at a party, at the club, at the theatre etc.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………………. the end, I got a visa for the UK.",
            "description": "In the end means after a long time.",
            "answers": [
                "On",
                "In",
                "At"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The movie is not very interesting ……………………………. the end.",
            "description": "At the end means at the point where something stops.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You look prettier ………………………………. this photo.",
            "description": "We say in a picture or in a photo.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you find a bird …………………………….. that picture?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "There is no room ………………………………. the bus.",
            "description": "We say ‘on a bus’.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The boys looked dapper …………………………….. their uniforms.",
            "description": "We say in a shirt, suit, hat, coat, uniform etc.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The meeting started ………………………………. time.",
            "description": "On time means at the planned time.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you talking ………………………………. such a loud voice?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "with",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}